# Andrii Kotov

Ivano-Frankivsk, Ukraine



hakoda.ak@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mhakoda



https://www.mhakoda.com

## Summary

I'm an entrepreneur, I write code to create great products for customers. I also develop my own commercial iOS application Fastriver, a new tool for e-commerce in Ukraine, allowing merchants to keep records of their goods and orders and track their payment and delivery.

Here are some great projects I've worked on, Mr Dicey, King Apdo, Say Me, Pleasant Space, and others. Developing and programming for the web and mobile devices has always been a pleasure for me. I was drawn into this industry by my brother, to whom I am very grateful for his support and help.

## **Experience**



## Web Developer

Altairlabs

Aug 2021 - Present (10 months +)



Sole Proprietor Jan 2019 - Dec 2020 (2 years)

#### **Education**



## 🕠 Ivan Franko National University of Lviv

**Business/Managerial Economics** Sep 2015 - Jul 2018 Some University Courses

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



Certificate of Completion - 100 Days of SwiftUI - Hacking with Swift

#### Skills

iOS Development • Swift • SwiftUI • Application Development • GitHub • Xcode • WebKit • Firebase